http://www.premiergolf.com/premier-golf-privacy-policy

HomeAbout Premier GolfMeet Our TeamTestimonialsTerms and ConditionsNews CenterContact Us
Sign up for our FREE eNewsletter
Call us at 866.260.4409 • Click Here to Start Planning Your Trip!Stay connected with us:
Premier Golf Domestic Privacy Policy
Premier Golf respects individual privacy and values the confidence of its customers. Premier Golf strives to collect, use and disclose Personal information in a manner consistent with state and federal privacy laws, as they apply, and has a tradition of upholding the highest ethical standards in its business practices. This Privacy Policy (the "Policy") sets forth the privacy principles that Premier Golf follows with respect to transfers of personal information anywhere in the United States.I. EnforcementPremier Golf has a Chief Privacy Officer who is responsible for Premier Golf's™ compliance with and enforcement of this Policy and data security issues. Premier Golf educates its employees concerning compliance with this Policy and has self-assessment procedures in place to assure compliance. Premier Golf's™ Chief Privacy Officer is available to any of its valued customers who may have questions concerning this Policy or data security practices. Relevant contact information is provided herein.II. ScopeThis Policy applies to all Personal information received by Premier Golf in any format including electronic, paper or verbal. Premier Golf collects and processes Personal information concerning its customers and potential customers manually and through its Internet site. As an integral part of its business, Premier Golf collects and processes Personal information from its customers in a variety of ways, including manually, via telephonic means (including facsimiles), electronic mail, the Internet or its Intranet site.Premier Golf will not sell or share this information with third parties in ways different than what are disclosed in this Privacy Policy. On a national basis, Premier Golf will, and will cause its affiliates and business partners to, establish and maintain business procedures that are consistent with this Policy.Personal information collected by Premier Golf from prospective customers and customers may be maintained at its National Support Center in Duluth, Georgia, or at its other sites. Premier Golf collects Personal information for, among other things, legitimate business reasons such as customer service, travel related reporting and records requirements, maintenance of accurate accounts payable and receivable records, and performance management, financial and sales data, and contact information. All Personal information collected by Premier Golf will be used for legitimate business purposes consistent with this Policy.III. DefinitionsFor purposes of this Policy, the following definitions shall apply:"Agent" means any third party that uses Personal information provided by Premier Golf to perform tasks on behalf of or at the instruction of Premier Golf."Premier Golf " means Premier Golf, its predecessors, successors, subsidiaries, parent company, divisions and groups."Personal information" means any information or set of information that identifies or could be used by or on behalf of Premier Golf to identify an individual. Personal information does not include information that is encoded or anonymized, or publicly available information that has not been combined with non-public Personal information.IV. Privacy PrinciplesDATA INTEGRITY: Premier Golf will use Personal information only in ways that are compatible with the purposes for which it was collected or subsequently authorized by our customers. Premier Golf will take reasonable steps to ensure that Personal information is relevant to its intended use, accurate, complete, and current.TRANSFERS TO AGENTS: Premier Golf will obtain assurances from its Agents that they will safeguard Personal information consistently with this Policy. Where Premier Golf has knowledge that an Agent is using or disclosing Personal information in a manner contrary to this Policy, Premier Golf will take reasonable steps to prevent or stop the use or disclosure. Premier Golf holds its Agents accountable for maintaining the trust its employees and customers place in the Company.ACCESS AND CORRECTION: Upon request, Premier Golf will grant individuals reasonable access to Personal information that it holds about them. In addition, Premier Golf will take reasonable steps to permit individuals to correct, amend, or delete information that is demonstrated to be inaccurate or incomplete. Any customer who desires to review, correct or delete their information can do so by contacting Premier Golf, Customer Development, 4355 River Green Parkway, Duluth, GA 30096.SECURITY: Premier Golf will take reasonable precautions to protect Personal information in its possession from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Security is designed to prevent unauthorized access to database equipment and hard copies of Personal information and monitors access to its servers to provide protection from hacking or other unauthorized access. Premier Golf limits access to Personal information and data to those persons in Premier Golf 's organization, or agents of Premier Golf, that have a specific business purpose for maintaining and processing such information and data. Individuals who have been granted access to Personal information are aware of their responsibilities to protect the security, confidentiality and integrity of that information.ENFORCEMENT: Global Premier Golf will conduct compliance audits of its relevant privacy practices to verify adherence to this Policy. Any employee who Premier Golf determines is in violation of this Policy will be subject to disciplinary action up to and including termination of employment.V. Dispute ResolutionAny questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of Personal Information should be directed to the Premier Golf Privacy Officer at Premier Golf, 4355 River Green Parkway, Duluth, GA 30096. Premier Golf will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of Personal information in accordance with the principles contained in this Policy.VI. Internet PrivacyPremier Golf sees the Internet, Intranets and the use of other technologies as valuable tools for communicating and interacting with consumers. Premier Golf recognizes the importance of maintaining the privacy of Personal information collected through Web Sites that it operates. Visitors on the Web may elect to voluntarily provide Personal information via Premier Golf Web sites but are not required to do so. In general, Premier Golf collects personal information for the purpose of maintaining an effective business relationship with our customers; i.e. to perform services contracted with our customers in our role as a Travel Management Company. Premier Golf does not permit any confidential company or Personal information of our customers to be shared with or sold to third parties. Premier Golf will only share such information with third parties at the specific written request of the customer, and/or as directed in legal contracts between the customer and a third party.Premier Golf respects the right to privacy of all individuals. However, in certain circumstances, we may disclose Personal information to government authorities or as dictated by legal obligation.Premier Golf may also collect anonymous information concerning Web site users through the use of "cookies". "Cookies" are small files that Web sites place on users' computers to identify the user and enhance the Web site experience. Visitors may set their browsers to provide notice before they receive a cookie, giving them opportunity to decide whether to accept the cookie. A visitor can also set their browser to turn off cookies. If visitors do so, however, some areas of Premier Golf Web sites may not function properly.Premier Golf customers have the option to request that Premier Golf not use information previously provided, correct information previously provided, or remove information previously provided to Premier Golf. Customers who would like to correct or suppress information they have provided to Premier Golf should forward such requests to Premier Golf, Customer Development, 4355 River Green Parkway, Duluth, GA 30096.Premier Golf Web sites may contain links to other "Non-Premier Golf" Web sites. Premier Golf assumes no responsibility for the content or the privacy policies and practices of those Web sites. Premier Golf encourages all users to read the privacy statements of those sites; their privacy practices may differ from those of Premier Golf.VII. Contact InformationPersons who wish to obtain access to their Personal information or Sensitive Personal information for purposes of correction or deletion should contact the following:Access, Correct or Delete Personal Information:Contact:Premier Golf, Customer Development, 4355 River Green Parkway, Duluth, GA 30096Persons who wish to resolve a dispute with Premier Golf over its Privacy Policy should contact the following:Dispute Resolution:Contact:Premier Golf, Chief Privacy Officer, 4355 River Green Parkway, Duluth, GA 30096VIII. Changes To This Privacy PolicyThe practices described in this Policy are current as of March 5, 2009. Premier Golf reserves the right to modify or amend this Policy at any time consistent with state and federal privacy laws, as they apply. Appropriate public notice will be given concerning such amendments.Premier Golf Global Privacy PolicyPremier Golf International, Inc. ("Premier Golf") respects individual privacy and values the confidence of its customers, employees, vendors, business partners and others. Premier Golf strives to collect, use and disclose Personal information in a manner consistent with the laws of the countries in which it does business and has a tradition of upholding the highest ethical standards in its business practices. Premier Golf abides by the Safe Harbor Principles developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission and the Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs) issued by the Department of Commerce on July 21, 2000. This Safe Harbor Privacy Policy (the "Policy") sets forth the privacy principles that Premier Golf follows with respect to transfers of Personal information anywhere in the world, including transfers from the European Economic Area (EEA) (which includes the twenty-five member states of the European Union (EU) plus Iceland, Liechtenstein and Norway) to the United States.I. Safe HarborThe United States Department of Commerce and the European Commission have agreed on a set of data protection principles and frequently asked questions (the "Safe Harbor Principles") to enable US companies to satisfy the requirement under European Union law that adequate protection be given to Personal information transferred from the EU to the United States. The European Economic Area ("EEA") also has recognized the US Safe Harbor as providing adequate data protection (OJ L 45, 15.2.2001, p.47). Consistent with its commitment to protect Personal privacy, Premier Golf adheres to the Safe Harbor Principles.Premier Golf has a Chief Privacy Officer who is responsible for Premier Golf's compliance with and enforcement of this Policy and data security issues. Premier Golf educates its employees concerning compliance with this Policy and has self-assessment procedures in place to assure compliance. Premier Golf's Chief Privacy Officer, Linwood Hayes is available to any of its valued customers, employees, vendors, business partners and others who may have questions concerning this Policy or data security practices. Relevant contact information is provided herein.II. ScopeThis Policy applies to all Personal information received by Premier Golf in any format including electronic, paper or verbal. Premier Golf collects and processes Personal information concerning its customers and potential customers manually and through its Internet site. As an integral part of its business, Premier Golf collects and processes Personal information from its customers in a variety of ways, including manually, via telephonic means (including facsimiles), electronic mail, the Internet or its Intranet site.Premier Golf will not sell or share this information with third parties in ways different than what are disclosed in this Privacy Policy. On a national basis, Premier Golf will, and will cause its affiliates and business partners to, establish and maintain business procedures that are consistent with this Policy.Personal information collected by Premier Golf from prospective customers and customers may be maintained at its National Support Center in Duluth, Georgia, or at its other sites. Premier Golf collects Personal information for, among other things, legitimate business reasons such as customer service, travel related reporting and records requirements, maintenance of accurate accounts payable and receivable records, and performance management, financial and sales data, and contact information. All Personal information collected by Premier Golf will be used for legitimate business purposes consistent with this Policy.III. DefinitionsFor purposes of this Policy, the following definitions shall apply: "Agent" means any third party that uses Personal information provided by Premier Golf to perform tasks on behalf of or at the instruction of Premier Golf."Premier Golf " means Premier Golf, its predecessors, successors, subsidiaries, parent company, divisions and groups."Personal information" means any information or set of information that identifies or could be used by or on behalf of Premier Golf to identify an individual. Personal information does not include information that is encoded or anonymized, or publicly available information that has not been combined with non-public Personal information.IV. Privacy PrinciplesThe privacy principles in this Policy are based on the seven Safe Harbor Principles.NOTICE: Where Premier Golf collects Personal information directly from individuals, it will inform them about the purposes for which it collects and uses Personal information about them, the types of non-agent third parties to which Premier Golf discloses that information, and the choices and means, if any, Premier Golf offers individuals for limiting the use and disclosure of their Personal information. Notice will be provided in clear and conspicuous language when individuals are first asked to provide Personal information to Premier Golf, or as soon as practicable thereafter, and in any event before Premier Golf uses the information for a purpose other than that for which it was originally collected. Premier Golf may disclose Personal information if required to do so by law or to protect and defend the rights or property of Premier Golf.CHOICE: Premier Golf will offer individuals the opportunity to choose (opt-out) whether their Personal information is (a) to be disclosed to a non-agent third party, or (b) to be used for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual.For Sensitive Personal information, Premier Golf will give individuals the opportunity to affirmatively and explicitly (opt-in) consent to the disclosure of the information to a non-agent third party or the use of the information for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual.Premier Golf will provide individuals with reasonable mechanisms to exercise their choices should requisite circumstances arise.DATA INTEGRITY: Premier Golf will use Personal information only in ways that are compatible with the purposes for which it was collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. Premier Golf will take reasonable steps to ensure that Personal information is relevant to its intended use, accurate, complete, and current.TRANSFERS TO AGENTS: Premier Golf will obtain assurances from its Agents that they will safeguard Personal information consistently with this Policy. Examples of appropriate assurances that may be provided by Agents include: a contract obligating the agent to provide at least the same level of protection as is required by the relevant Safe Harbor Principles, being subject to EU Directive 95/46/EC (the EU Data Protection Directive), Safe Harbor certification by the agent, or being subject to another European Commission adequacy finding (e.g., companies located in Hungary and Switzerland). Where Premier Golf has knowledge that an Agent is using or disclosing Personal information in a manner contrary to this Policy, Premier Golf will take reasonable steps to prevent or stop the use or disclosure. Premier Golf holds it Agents accountable for maintaining the trust its employees and customers place in the company.ACCESS AND CORRECTION: Upon request, Premier Golf will grant individuals reasonable access to Personal information that it holds about them. In addition, Premier Golf will take reasonable steps to permit individuals to correct, amend, or delete information that is demonstrated to be inaccurate or incomplete. Any customer who desires to review, correct or delete their information can do so by contacting Premier Golf, Customer Development, 4355 River Green Parkway, Duluth, GA 30096 USA, verifying their identity and providing their corporate account.SECURITY: Premier Golf will take reasonable precautions to protect Personal information in its possession from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Security is designed to prevent unauthorized access to database equipment and hard copies of Sensitive Personal information and monitors access to its servers to provide protection from hacking or other unauthorized access. Premier Golf limits access to Personal information and data to those persons in Premier Golf's organization, or agents of Premier Golf, that have a specific business purpose for maintaining and processing such information and data. Individuals who have been granted access to Personal information are aware of their responsibilities to protect the security, confidentiality and integrity of that information.ENFORCEMENT: Premier Golf will conduct compliance audits of its relevant privacy practices to verify adherence to this Policy and the US Department of Commerce Safe Harbor Principles. Any employee who Premier Golf determines is in violation of this policy will be subject to disciplinary action up to and including termination of employment.V. Dispute ResolutionAny questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of Personal Information should be directed to the Premier Golf Privacy Officer at Premier Golf, 4355 River Green Parkway, Duluth, GA 30096. Premier Golf will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of Personal information in accordance with the principles contained in this Policy. For complaints that cannot be resolved between Premier Golf and the complainant, Premier Golf has agreed to participate in the dispute resolution procedures of the panel established by the European data protection authorities to resolve disputes pursuant to the Safe Harbor Principles.VI. Internet PrivacyPremier Golf sees the Internet, Intranets and the use of other technologies as valuable tools for communicating and interacting with consumers. Premier Golf recognizes the importance of maintaining the privacy of Personal information collected through Web Sites that it operates. Visitors on the Web may elect to voluntarily provide Personal information via Premier Golf Web sites but are not required to do so. In general, Premier Golf collects personal information for the purpose of maintaining an effective business relationship with our customers; i.e. to perform services contracted with our customers in our role as a Travel Management Company. Premier Golf does not permit any confidential company or Personal information of our customers to be shared with or sold to third parties. Premier Golf will only share such information with third parties at the specific written request of the customer, and/or as directed in legal contracts between the customer and a third party.Premier Golf respects the right to privacy of all individuals. However, in certain circumstances, we may disclose Personal information to government authorities or as dictated by legal obligation.Premier Golf may also collect anonymous information concerning Web site users through the use of "cookies". "Cookies" are small files that Web sites place on users' computers to identify the user and enhance the Web site experience. Visitors may set their browsers to provide notice before they receive a cookie, giving them opportunity to decide whether to accept the cookie. A visitor can also set their browser to turn off cookies. If visitors do so, however, some areas of Premier Golf Web sites may not function properly.Premier Golf customers have the option to request that Premier Golf not use information previously provided, correct information previously provided, or remove information previously provided to Premier Golf. Customers who would like to correct or suppress information they have provided to Premier Golf should forward such requests to Premier Golf, Customer Development, 4355 River Green Parkway, Duluth, GA 30096.Premier Golf Web sites may contain links to other "Non-Premier Golf" Web sites. Premier Golf assumes no responsibility for the content or the privacy policies and practices of those Web sites. Premier Golf encourages all users to read the privacy statements of those sites; their privacy practices may differ from those of Premier Golf.VII. Contact InformationPersons who wish to obtain access to their Personal information or Sensitive Personal information for purposes of correction or deletion should contact the following:Access, Correct or Delete Personal Information:Contact:Premier Golf, Customer Development, 4355 River Green Parkway, Duluth, GA 30096Persons who wish to resolve a dispute with Premier Golf over its Privacy Policy should contact the following:Dispute ResolutionContact: Premier Golf, Chief Privacy Officer, 4355 River Green Parkway, Duluth, GA 30096EmployeesContact:Human Resources RepresentativeEmployee's Local OfficeVIII. Changes to this Safe Harbor Privacy PolicyThe practices described in this Policy are current Personal data protection policies as of March 5, 2009. Premier Golf reserves the right to modify or amend this Policy at any time consistent with the requirements of the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework. Appropriate public notice will be given concerning such amendments.IX. Safe Harbor EnforcementPremier Golf is compliant under U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework as outlined by the U.S. Department of Commerce. Any disputes that arrive from the passing of personal information will be investigated and resolved.Mail to:Chief Privacy OfficerPremier Golf4355 River Green ParkwayDuluth, Georgia 30096Web site URL: http://www.PremierGolf.com
Click here to inquire today!
Stay connected with us:
PGA Merchandise Show, January 22-25, 2019 in Orlando, FL. Read highlights.
Book With Confidence + Travel Updates
Stay informed on the latest news, events and deals from Premier Golf with our eNewsletter!
Sign up today!
You need to be 100% focused on your game to play a great round of golf by avoiding countless hazards on and off the course. That is why TravelSafe created a product specifically for the modern golfer – GolfSafe Travel Protection.
At Ship Sticks, we make getting your golf clubs to and from your destination easier than it's ever been – allowing you to enjoy a hassle-free travel experience to anywhere in the world.
©
Premier Golf. All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy   |   Site Map   |
Website Credits
Interested in golf?
×
Sign up for our Golf Travel Buzz Newsletter & Blog.
Slide in (right)
